Guide to the Bob Fitch Photography Archive M1994
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 1: Subject Files, 1960-2016; 23 Linear Feet 43 manuscript boxes
  - Day, Dorothy [prints], 1969-1974 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Prints are numbered 3088-3091, 3093, 3099-3101, 3103-3106, 3108-3110, 3113, 3115, 3117-3119, 3584, 3585.
  - Day, Dorothy: Photo identifications, 2007-2014 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Day, Dorothy: Correspondence and notes, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Day, Dorothy: Claudia - new [prints], 1969-1974 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Prints are numbered 3101, 3114, 3119.
  - Day, Dorothy: Claudia - use [prints], 1969-1974 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Prints are numbered 3090, 3093, 3105, 3106, 3109, 3584, 3895.
  - Day, Dorothy: Claudia - use [prints], 1969-1974 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Prints are numbered 3113, 3884.
  - Days [negatives], 1960-2016 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Debbie [contact sheets], 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Contact sheet is numbered 4140.
  - Dellums, Ron: Photo index, 1970-1974 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Dellums, Ron: Photo identifications [contact sheets], 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Ron Dellums campaigning for congress and meeting constituents, with his family and with Julian Bond, Willie Brown, Bill Russell, Ken Meade, Weldon Rucker, Mervyn Dymally, Reverend Cecil Williams and Joe Dohrn. Includes notes identifying people, places and dates.
    Contact sheets are numbered 1663, 1664, 2041-2044, 2107-2109, 2111.
  - Dellums, Ron: Photo identifications [contact sheets], 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    Ron Dellums campaigning for congress and meeting constituents, with his family and with Julian Bond, Willie Brown, Dolores Huerta, Craig Morris, Fred Williamson and Fred Harris. Includes notes identifying people, places and dates.
    Sheets are numbered 2112, 2114, 2115, 2117, 2118, 2144, 2145, 2149, 2192, 2193.
  - Dellums, Ron: Photo identifications [contact sheets], 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    Ron Dellums campaigning for congress and meeting constituents, with his family and with Weldon Rucker, George McGovern, Phillip Burton, Kermit Scott and John DeBonis. Includes notes identifying people, places and dates.
    Contact sheets are numbered 2199, 2202, 2203, 2210, 2237, 2238, 2240, 2241, 2243, 2245.
  - Dellums, Ron: Photo identifications [contact sheets], 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    Ron Dellums campaigning for congress and meeting constituents, with his family and with Weldon Rucker, Paul Cobb, Willie Brown, Cesar Chavez, Elijah Turner, Edith Austin, Norvell Smith, Roscoe Dellums and Theresa Verney. Includes notes identifying people, places and dates.
    Sheets are numbered 2248, 2260, 2274, 2276, 2284-2286, 2289, 2295.
  - Dellums, Ron: Photo identifications [contact sheets], 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    Ron Dellums campaigning for congress and meeting constituents, with his family and with Coretta Scott King, Roscoe Dellums, Booker Anderson, Nicholas Petris, Fred Wyatt, Tom Berkeley, Paul Cobb, Warren Widener, John DeBonis, Bella Abzug, Shirley Chisholm and Bordon Price. Includes notes identifying people, places and dates.
    Contact sheets are numbered 2296, 2297, 2301, 2302, 2305, 2306, 2321, 2338, 2491, 2492, 2497.
  - Dellums, Ron: Photo identifications [contact sheets], 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    Ron Dellums campaigning for congress and meeting constituents, with his family and with Bella Abzug, Mike Duberstine and Shirley Chisholm. Includes notes identifying people, places and dates.
    Sheets are numbered 2499, 2503, 2504, 2506, 2507, 2509, 2515, 2524, 2540.
  - Dellums, Ron [contact sheets], 1970 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    Contact sheets are numbered 1660-1669, 1687-1691.
  - Dellums, Ron [contact sheets], 1970 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    Contact sheets are numbered 2036-2044.
  - Dellums, Ron [contact sheets], 1970 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Contact sheets are numbered 2106-2118.
  - Dellums, Ron [contact sheets], 1970 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Contact sheets are numbered 2144-2150, 2152, 2166, 2187, 2189-2195.
  - Dellums, Ron [contact sheets], 1970 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Contact sheets are numbered 2200-2212.
  - Dellums, Ron [contact sheets], 1970 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Contact sheets are numbered 2234-2256.
  - Dellums, Ron [contact sheets], 1970 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    Contact sheets are numbered 2257-2280.
  - Dellums, Ron [contact sheets], 1970 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Contact sheets are numbered 2281-2302.
  - Dellums, Ron [contact sheets], 1970 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    Contact sheets are numbered 2303-2306, 2316, 2318-2322, 2324-2326.
  - Dellums, Ron [contact sheets], 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    Contact sheets are numbered 2373-2375, 2377, 2379-2386, 2447-2450.
  - Dellums, Ron [contact sheets], 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    Contact sheets are numbered 2500, 2501, 2508, 2510, 2511, 2522, 2523, 2533-2543, 2572, 2575, 2586, 2587, 2627, 2641, 2709, 2906, 2907, 2913, 3393, 3589, 3622.
  - Dellums, Ron [prints] [part 1 of 2], 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    Prints are numbered 1660, 1662, 1664, 2031, 2036, 2042-2044, 2108, 2111, 2112, 2114, 2115, 2148, 2152, 2166, 2187, 2200, 2203, 2235, 2244, 2252, 2253, 2255, 2260, 2261, 2278-2280, 2285, 2286, 2288, 2294, 2297, 2306, 2380, 2382-2385, 2447-2449, 2501, 2512, 2517, 2524, 2777, 2779, 3155, 3393, 3395, 3408/
  - Dellums, Ron [prints] [part 2 of 2], 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Prints are numbered 1660, 1662, 1664, 2031, 2036, 2042-2044, 2108, 2111, 2112, 2114, 2115, 2148, 2152, 2166, 2187, 2200, 2203, 2235, 2244, 2252, 2253, 2255, 2260, 2261, 2278-2280, 2285, 2286, 2288, 2294, 2297, 2306, 2380, 2382-2385, 2447-2449, 2501, 2512, 2517, 2524, 2777, 2779, 3155, 3393, 3395, 3408.
  - Dellums, Ron: Campaign [slides], 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Dellums, Ron: Washington D.C. [contact sheets], 1971 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Contact sheets are numbered 2488, 2492, 2495-2499, 2502, 2504-2506, 2509, 2512-2521, 2524.
  - Dellums, Ron: Press conference, Washington D.C. [slides], 1971 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Dellums, Ron: Press conference, Oakland, California [contact sheets], February 8, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    Ron Dellums at a press conference and his office with staff, including Don Hopkins, Roberta Brooks, Mary Thomas, Larry Green, James Petersen and Lee Halterman and other candidates, including Paul Cobb, Warren Widener and Alphonso Galloway.
    Contact sheets are numbered 2573-2576.
  - Dellums, Ron: Debate with Wilmont Sweeney, Berkeley, California [contact sheets], March, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Congressman Ron Dellums campaigning for the April Coalition and the Community Control of Police initiative debating Wilmont Sweeney during municipal elections, Berkeley, California.
    Contacts sheets are numbered 2777-2779.
  - Dellums, Ron: with Shirley Chisholm [contact sheets], November, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    Contact sheet is numbered 3155.
  - Dellums, Ron: Campaigning at the University of California Berkeley campus, Berkeley, California [contact sheets], December, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3219, 3220.
  - Dellums, Ron: Campaign Press conference [contact sheets], 1972 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3281, 3282, 3326.
  - Dellums, Ron: Oakland Post Office, Oakland, California [contact sheets], February, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3391, 3392, 3394-3399.
  - Dellums, Ron: San Quentin Prison, California [contact sheets], September, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3406, 3411, 3412.
  - Dellums, Ron: Victory, Oakland, California [contact sheets], November 11, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    Contact sheets are numbered 2253, 2254, 2256, 2267, 3535-3538.
  - Dellums, Ron: D.C. staff [contact sheets], January 5, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3589, 3590, 3622.
  - Dellums, Ron: Office of Economic Opportunity [contact sheets], April, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    Contact sheet is numbered 3743.
  - Dellums, Ron: with Andrew Young, Oakland, California [contact sheets], October 20, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4068, 4069.
  - Dellums, Ron: Campaign headquarters, Oakland, California [contact sheets], April, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4188-4190.
  - Dellums, Ron: Fundraiser with Jesse Jackson and Shirley Chisholm [contact sheets], 1972 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    Ron Dellums with Shirley Chisholm, Jesse Jackson and Bobby Seale during a fundraiser.
    Contact sheets are numbered 3393, 3407-3409, 3415, 3416.
  - Dellums, Ron: Scanned images [prints], 1970-1974 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    Prints are numbered 1668, 2037, 2041, 2043, 2044, 2106, 2109, 2110, 2112, 2114, 2118, 2149, 2187, 2193, 2203, 2207, 2228, 2235, 2241, 2245, 2250, 2253, 2255, 2260, 2278, 2280, 2288, 2289, 2297, 2448, 2449, 2503, 2509, 2512, 2513, 2535, 2799, 3155, 3393, 3407, 3408, 3590.
  - Dellums, Ron: Scanned images [prints], 1970-1974 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    Prints are numbered 1661-1663, 1667, 1668, 2108, 2111, 2149, 2166, 2187, 2203, 2233, 2238, 2240, 2253, 2255, 2265, 2268, 2275, 2278-2280, 2288, 2297, 2449, 2807, 3393, 3589, 3590.
  - Dellums, Ron: Images for Stanford Web [slides], 1968-1972 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Delta Trucking Lines [contact sheets], 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4539-4558.
  - Devereaux, Don: Investigative reporter, Santa Fe, New Mexico [contact sheets], 1974, 2014 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4244, 4249.
  - Devereaux, Don: Investigative reporter, Santa Fe, New Mexico [slides], 1974 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Devlin, Bernadette, San Francisco Bay Area, California [slides], 1971 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Display [contact sheets], 1970 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Contact sheet is numbered 2371.
  - Ditch/garden, Weed, California [contact sheets], May, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    Contact sheet is numbered 5606.
  - Don & Remhardt auto repair garage [contact sheets], August, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    Contact sheets are numbered 1970, 1971.
  - Dorothy's Place: Soup kitchen, Salinas, California [prints], 1999-2016 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Dorothy's Place/Loaves and Fishes, Salinas, California [prints], 1999-2016 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Dotter, Earl: Photojournalist [correspondence], 2008 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Dougherty, Molly [contact sheets], July 19, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    Content sheets are numbered 4278, 4279.
  - Drotl [contact sheets], October 21, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4060, 4061.
  - Duke City Lumber, Albuquerque, New Mexico [contact sheets], May, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4217-4220.
  - Durango, Colorado: Fire [contact sheets], June, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4259.
  - Dwight House [contact sheets], 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    Contact sheet is numbered 880.
  - East Bay School, California [contact sheets], August, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4173, 4174, 4187.
  - Easter march: Seminarians/Catonsville 9 status, Oakland, California [contact sheets], March, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3311, 3312, 3315.
  - Ebony [contact sheets], December, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4098-4101.
  - Ecology: Trash and tires in wetlands, Union City, California [contact sheets], July, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    Contact sheet is numbered 2900.
  - El Jarrah, Vicci [contact sheets], 1968 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    Contact sheets are numbered 597-602.
  - Ellsberg, Daniel at his home, Malibu, California [contact sheets], September 6, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4034-4036.
  - Ellsberg, Daniel at his home, Malibu, California [slides], September 6, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Ellsberg, Daniel with Joan Baez and others at the War Resisters League 50th anniversary, Asilomar, California [prints], August, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - English Center for Non-Violence [contact sheets], March 14, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    Contact sheet is numbered 5764.
  - Episcopal women [contact sheets], January 31, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4123-4126.
  - Episcopal, Northern California [contact sheets], 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4050, 4051, 4131.
  - Erotic Museum: Opening and press conference, San Francisco [contact sheets], March, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3688-3690, 3695-3697.
  - Erotic Museum: Opening and press conference, San Francisco [slides], March, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Erotic Museum, San Francisco, California [contact sheets], June, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3890, 3891.
  - Esberg, Judy [contact sheets], October, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    Contact sheet is numbered 3529.
  - Escalator, Penn Station, New York City, New York [contact sheets], January 8, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    Contact sheet is numbered 3588.
  - Eskaton [prints], 1970-1976 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    Prints are numbered 1999, 2002, 2003, 2005-2007, 2355, 2362, 2459, 4037, 4415, 4487.
  - Exhibit: Bob Fitch United Farm Workers exhibit, University of California, Santa Barbara [contact sheets], 1973 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4038, 4045.
  - Families: Man and woman [prints], 1966-1978 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    Prints are numbered 185, 224, 229, 230, 240, 351, 375, 513, 540, 543, 637, 760, 907, 929, 933, 1517, 1518, 1526, 2530, 1600, 1602, 1849, 1884, 1897, 2187, 2237, 3482, 2578, 2780, 2839, 2853, 2858, 2863, 2865, 2876, 2889, 2952, 3076, 3261, 3318, 3410, 3491, 3516, 3525, 3605, 3640, 3641, 3784, 4229, 4231, 4248, 4249, 4252, 4399, 4406, 4407, 4412, 4413, 4424, 5547.
  - Famous [prints], 1960-2016 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Includes images of Jane Fonda, Beniamino Bufano, Stokely Carmichael, Daniel Ellsberg, Allen Ginsberg, Cecil Williams, Adam Clayton Powell.
  - Farms [contact sheets], 1968-1970 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    Contact sheets are numbered 1456, 1458.
  - Farmworkers: articles and notes, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Fenley, L.J. [prints], 1960-2016 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Fernandez, Benedict: Workshop [contact sheets and interview notes], 1972 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3338-3341.
  - Ferry: Golden Gate Ferry, San Francisco Bay, California [contact sheets], October, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3522, 3523, 3525.
  - Fire/firefighters [prints], 1971 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Prints are numbered 2692.
  - Fire/firefighters [slides], 1971 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Fisher, Margot [contact sheets], 1971 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    Contact sheet is numbered 2559.
  - Fisherman's Wharf, San Francisco, California [contact sheets], June, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    Contact sheet is numbered 4275.
  - Fitch, Benjamin [contact sheets], 1971-1980 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3153, 3218, 3249, 3291, 3302, 3305, 3874, 4364, 4501, 5482, 5706.
  - Fitch, Benjamin [prints], 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Fitch, Bob: Early photos [slides], 1961-1964 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Fitch, Bob [contact sheets], 1966-1978 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    Contact sheets are numbered 260, 543, 1793, 3560, 3623, 4062, 4063, 4445, 4510, 4512, 4562, 5478, 5515.
  - Fitch, Bob: Birthday party [contact sheets], 1970 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    Contact sheet is numbered 1931.
  - Fitch, Bob [slides], 1978 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Fitch, Bob [prints], 1960-2016 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Fitch, Bob: Family [contact sheets], 1974-1980 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4270, 5500, 5727.
  - Fitch, Bob: Family [prints], 1960-2016 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Fitch, Bob: Family [prints], 1973-2003 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    Prints are numbered 5531, 5760, 5762, 5772, 5774, 5777, 5782, 5831, 5834, 5843, 5913, 5919, 5924, 6022, 6055, 6066, 6087.
  - Fitch, Bob: Family [prints], 1960-2016 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    Prints are numbered 5872, 2884, 2885, 5938.
  - Fitch, Bob: Yosemite [prints], 1990 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    Prints are numbered 5761, 5762.
  - Fitch, Bob: Family Christmas [contact sheets], 1967 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    Contact sheets are numbered 166, 337, 367, 378, 385, 414, 418, 434, 435, 438, 439, 441, 443, 447, 961.
  - Fitch, Bob: Family Christmas [contact sheets], 1968 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    Contact sheets are numbered 784-791.
  - Fitch, Bob: Family Christmas [contact sheets], 1969 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Contact sheets are numbered 1536, 1538, 1539, 1540, 1542.
  - Fitch, Bob: Family Christmas [contact sheets], 1970 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Contact sheet is numbered 2446.
  - Fitch, Bob: Family Christmas [contact sheets], 1971 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Contact sheets are numbered 3232, 3233.
  - Fitch, Bob: Family Christmas [contact sheets], 1975 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4431, 4432.
  - Fitch, Bob: Family Christmas [contact sheets], 1978 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Contact sheet is numbered 5603.
  - Fitch, Bob: Family Christmas [prints], 1981 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Fitch, Bob: Family Christmas [prints], 1986 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Fitch, Bob: Family [slides] [part 1 of 2], 1967-1980 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Fitch, Bob: Family [slides] [part 2 of 2], 1967-1980 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Fitch, Bob: Miscellaneous family photos [prints], 1980-1987 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Fitch, Bob: Friends [prints], 1996-2002 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    Prints are numbered 5842, 6055.
  - Fitch, Bob: Friends [prints] [part 1 of 2], 1980-2004 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    Prints are numbered 5755, 5761, 5762, 5771, 5776, 5805, 5835, 5836, 5839-5842, 5846-5848, 5854, 5873, 5875, 5884, 5889, 5910, 5911, 5913, 5931, 5974, 5982, 5995, 5996, 6004, 6069, 6193.
  - Fitch, Bob: Friends [prints] [part 2 of 2], 1980-2004 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Fitch, Bob: Friends [prints], 1990-2001 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Prints are numbered 5842, 6055]
  - Fitch, Bob: Friends [prints], 1978-2004 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    Prints are numbered 5197, 5783, 5809, 5818, 5839, 5847, 5920, 5996, 6022, 6026, 6041, 6065, 6070, 6230.
  - Fitch, Bob: Friends [prints], 1989-1999 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    Prints are numbered 5755, 5757, 5763, 5769, 5771, 5782, 5801, 5805, 5807, 5813, 5814, 5835, 5838, 5839, 5845, 5848, 5866, 5873, 5876, 5878, 5883, 5910, 5920, 5921, 5925.
  - Fitch, Bob: Kent Miles photograph of Bob Fitch [prints], 1960-2016 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Fitch, Bob: Parents [contact sheets], 1970 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    Contact sheets are numbered 1550, 1553, 2446.
  - Fitch, Bob: Parents' wedding anniversary [negatives], 1960-2016 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Fitch, Bob: Sweet friends [prints], 1990-1999 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Prints are numbered 5763, 5771, 5773, 5780, 5781, 5801, 5803, 5804, 5814, 5837, 5866, 5867, 5868, 5877, 5878, 5882.
  - Fitch, Bob: Sweets, George and other family animals [contact sheets], 1978-1980 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    Contact sheets are numbered 4559, 4560, 5480, 5490, 5666, 5732.
  - Fitch, Bob: California Song Festival [prints], May, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    Prints are numbered 5829-5832.
  - Fitch, Bob: San Francisco Folk Music Camp [prints], 1993 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    Print is numbered 5835.
  - Fitch, Bob: Housing and Community Development party and picnic [prints], 1993 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    Prints are numbered 5837, 5841, 5843.
  - Fitch, Bob: Yangzhou, China [prints], 1994 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    Prints are numbered 5849, 5862, 5865.
  - Fitch, Bob: Hong Kong [prints], 1994 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    Prints are numbered 5853.
  - Fitch, Bob: North Island, New Zealand [prints], 1994 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    Prints are numbered 5850, 5853, 5856, 5857, 5858, 5862, 5864.
  - Fitch, Bob: Lake Taupo, New Zealand [prints], 1994 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    Prints are numbered 5854-5859.
  - Fitch, Bob: Fjords, New Zealand [prints], 1994 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Prints are numbered 5855.
  - Fitch, Bob: Picton, New Zealand [prints], 1994 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    Prints are numbered 5860, 5861.
  - Fitch, Bob: China and New Zealand [prints], July, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    Prints are numbered 5862.
  - Fitch, Bob: Rotorua, New Zealand [prints], 1994 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    Prints are numbered 5852, 5859.
  - Fitch, Bob: Kung Ming, China [prints], 1994 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    Prints are numbered 5865.
  - Fitch, Bob: New Zealand and Hong Kong [prints], 1994 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Fitch, Bob: Wellington, New Zealand [prints], 1994 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    Prints are numbered 5861.
  - Fitch, Bob: Woolworths, New Zealand [prints], 1994 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    Prints are numbered 5858-5864.
  - Fitch, Bob: Canton, China [prints], 1994 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    Prints are numbered 5849-5853.
  - Fitch, Bob: British Columbia Canada Folk Music Camp [prints] [part 1 of 2], 1995 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    Prints are numbered 5866, 5868-5870, 5872, 5909.
  - Fitch, Bob: British Columbia Canada Folk Music Camp [prints] [part 2 of 2], 1995 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Fitch, Bob: Sacramento house, California [prints], 1995 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    Prints are numbered 5873.
  - Fitch, Bob: Ben [Montana] and Sacramento friends [prints], 1997 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    Prints are numbered 5915.
  - Fitch, Bob: Emily birthday [prints], November, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    Prints are numbered 5889, 5890.
  - Fitch, Bob: Modesto Peace Camp [prints], July, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    Prints are numbered 5893.
  - Fitch, Bob: Ted and Ann wedding [prints], July, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Fitch, Bob: Goodbye party [prints], September, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Fitch, Bob [prints], 1996-1999 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    Prints are numbered 5910, 5919, 5921, 5922, 5925, 5937, 5939.
  - Fitch, Bob: Bellingham, Washington [prints], 1996 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    Prints are numbered 5889, 5896.
  - Fitch, Bob: House, Bellingham, Washington [prints], November, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Prints are numbered 5889.
  - Fitch, Bob: Bellingham, Washington [prints], 1997 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Prints are numbered 5914.
  - Fitch, Bob: Miscellaneous [prints], 1997 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Prints are numbered 5909, 5910.
  - Fitch, Bob: Swimming [prints], 1997-1999 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Fitch, Bob: Homes, Los Angeles, California [contact sheets], 1999 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Contact sheets are numbered 5934, 5935.
  - Fitch, Bob: 60th birthday party [contact sheets], 1999 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    Contact sheets are numbered 5941.
  - Fitch, Bob: 60th birthday party [prints] [part 1 of 2], 1999 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    Prints are numbered 5937, 5940.
  - Fitch, Bob: 60th birthday party [prints] [part 2 of 2], 1999 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    Prints are numbered 5938, 5939.
  - Fitch, Bob: Family and friends [contact sheets], 2002 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    Contact sheets are numbered 6022.
  - Fitch, Bob: Christmas [contact sheets], 2003 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    Contact sheets are numbered 6097, 6098.
  - Fitch, Bob: Beach house, Del Mar, California [contact sheets] [RESTRICTED], February, 2004 (Box 135, Folder 3)
    The materials in this file are restricted until January 1, 2084.
    Contact sheets are numbered 6108-6111.
  - Fitch, Bob: Apartment [contact sheets], April 11, 2013 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    Contact sheets are numbered 6212.
  - Fitch, Bob: Biographies and memorial service, 2006-2016 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Fitch, Bob: Freedom of Information requests, 1965-1982 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Fitch, Bob: Press cards, 1960-2016 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Fitch, Bob: Publicity [news clippings and correspondence], 1998-2008 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Fitch, Bob: Resume, 1980-2016 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Fitch, Bob: Signature and other graphics, 1960-2016 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Fitch, Bob: Scrapbook, 1967-1970 (Box 127, Item 1)
  - Fitch, Bob: Susan Hall research paper on Bob Fitch, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Fitch, Bob: Thank you letters from students, 2000-2011 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Fitch, Bob: Thank you letters from students, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 20)